paymentservicenetwork.com 2006-10-31

# Your online payment service for paying rent to landlords, lodging to bed and breakfast or association dues.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information:**

We collect personally identifiable information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address, bank account information, credit card numbers) from you when you set up an account with PSN. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as setting up recurring payments, receiving e-mail reminders, and viewing reports) do require registration. 

PSN does not sell, share, or in any other way transmit personally identifiable information (names, address, phone numbers, etc.) to any persons or companies outside the "PSN Family of Companies." The "PSN Family of Companies" are all subject to the same privacy policy and security measures as PaymentServiceNetwork.com. We do use your contact information to send you promotional products and information on behalf of our partner companies. 

**PSN Payers:**  
Our site requires you to give us contact information (name, address, phone number, and e-mail address) and billing information. We use your contact information to verify your identity, send you messages about your transaction or our company. 

We use your billing and financial information (bank account numbers) to facilitate payments through the PSN sites and collect fees if applicable. 

Payment Service Network will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:   
(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Payment Service Network; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Payment Service Network or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Payment Service Network, its web sites, or the public. 

**PSN Owners & Managers:**  
Our site's registration form requires you to give us contact information (name, address, phone number, and e-mail address) and billing information. We use your contact information to establish and/or verify your identity, and to notify you about payments processed from PSN Renters who are residents at your properties. 

We use your billing and financial information (bank account numbers) to facilitate payments through the PSN sites and collect fees if applicable. 

**Use of Demographic and Profile Data:**

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Web site. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.   
We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in -- and to display content according to your preferences. 

We sometimes use contact data from our surveys to send you information about our company and/or promotional material on behalf of our partners. 

**Security Precautions**

Security of Your Personal Information  
Payment Service Network is committed to helping protect the security of the personal information you provide. Personal information we collect is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access, and we use a variety of technologies and procedures to help protect this information from loss or misuse, and from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Our secure server software uses the SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) protocol, which completely encrypts all of your information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address, bank account information, credit card numbers) when it is sent between your computer and our server. This maintains the privacy, authenticity and integrity of your information before it sent to us, making it virtually impossible to intercept during transmission. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

**Correct, Review, Update or Delete Your Account Information**   
PSN provides all users with the opportunity to correct or update password-protected information stored in their account. 

**Contact Us**  
Please contact us with any questions about this Privacy Statement, our policies, and Security practices. 

Send your questions or feedback to:  
[suggestions@PaymentServiceNetwork.com.](mailto:suggestions@PaymentServiceNetwork.com) We want to hear from you.
